

MY CONTACT

Phone +63 949 329 7381

Email

businessforyang101@gmail.com

Address

Cebu City, Philippines 6000

EXPERTISE

- Visual design
- Salesforce
- Data Management
- Email Management
- Real Estate
- CRM
- CAD

SKILLS

- Excellent time management
- Leadership skills
- Computer skills
- Communication skills
- Data Analysis
- Data Cleaning
- Data Visualization
- R programming
- Data-driven decision making
- Calculation and analysis in SQL and spreadsheets

GUALBERTO OYANGOREN

ABOUT MYSELF

Versatile individual with experience collecting, transforming, and organizing data for analysis to help make informed decisions. Excellent understanding and proficiency of platforms for effective data analyses, including SQL, spreadsheets, Tableau, and R. Strong communication, organizational, and analytical skills. Has experience with client support as Global Client Operations of Hotelbeds. Recently completed the Google Data Analytics Certificate-a rigorous, handson program that covers the entire scope of the data analysis process.

EXPERIENCE

Hotelbeds Group | 2023-2024

Global Client Operations Executive

- Answering to emails
- Doing outbound calls to suppliers
- Taking inbound calls from clients or business partners.
- Insure guest can check-in at hotel as per clients and/or business partner's request.
- Use Salesforce and Outlook to manage emails.
- Use Tableau to analyzed data and create data visualization.

B. Vicencio Builders, Inc. | 2018-2023

Engineer

- Managing construction and real estate projects.
- Designing real estate projects and meet up potential clients to discuss projects.
- Manage cost for projects and salary of the workers.
- Use spreadsheets to sort and filter data.
- Clean data in spreadsheets.
- Design architectural projects using CAD software.
- Design structural elements using BIM software and other structural analysis software.

Google | January 2024-March 2024

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate

XSTRUCTURES ENGINEERING CONSULTANTS | December 2020

Autodesk 2D and 3D Training

Digiscript Philippines Inc. | March 2018

3D HIGH DEFINITION SURVEY

Leica Geosystems ScanStation P30 Training

EDUCATION

2018-2023

Graduate of Bachelor of Science in Civil Engineering - Major in Construction Management

Northwest Samar State University

2013-2018

School Boystown, Inc.

Graduate of Senior high school and Junior high school with various Tech-Voc courses taken: Sisters of Mary Technical Drafting NC II, Computer System Servicing NC II, and Automotive Servicing NC II.